freestylephoto.biz 2019-11-10

# Freestyle Privacy Policy | Freestyle Photographic Supplies

Below is Freestyle Photographic Supplies privacy notice. We value the trust and confidence you have in us that we will respect your privacy and handle your information in a responsible manner. By visiting Freestylephoto.biz, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy notice. 

Freestyle Photographic Supplies Corporate Headquarters: 

5124 Sunset Boulevard  
Hollywood, CA 90027  
Ph: (323) 660-3460  
Fax: (323) 284-0050   
Contact: [info@freestylephoto.biz](mailto:info@freestylephoto.biz)

If you have any concerns about our privacy notice, please contact us at the above corporate address, email address, phone or fax numbers. 

Personal Information We Collect  
The information you provide us helps us personalize and improve your shopping experience. 

We store all information that you enter on our Web site. If you choose not to provide certain information, it may inhibit our ability to properly service your needs. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as answering your questions and requests, shipping your products and communicating to you about your order(s) and any special offers that we may have. 

There are certain types of information that we store when you visit our site. Like many web sites, we use "cookies" to track information about how you use our site and to make return visits to our site more convenient. The Help button of the toolbar on most browsers can tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies. There are also several companies that offer utilities that will help you to visit Web sites anonymously. It is your right to use these tools while visiting our site. Please note that we may not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if you utilize these tools. 

Do We Share Information?   
The information that you give us remains confidential and is not sold to other companies for any reason, including solicitation. If our policy changes, you will receive notification prior to your information being shared with a third party, and you will have an opportunity to block your information from being released. 

Security of Your Information  
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using encryption software. This encryption protects information that you input. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card when confirming an order back to you. Please note that we do have to transmit the entire credit card number to the credit card company while processing your order. 

Shared Computers  
In order to protect your private information when using a shared or public computer, be sure to Log Off of our site when you have finished shopping with us. The Log Off button is located on our home page just above the Search button. 

Children  
Freestylephoto.biz does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18 years of age, you may use Freestylephoto.biz only with the consent of a parent or guardian.
